Facilities Management Department fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Departmental files, 1960 - 2003; F-11-3; 3 m of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the operations, policies and procedures of Facilities Management, including committee meetings, the delivery of ancillary services, and the design and construction of buildings and grounds. It includes agenda and minutes of meetings, certificates, contracts, correspondence, drawings, memoranda, and annual and other reports.
  Original order was lost and files were organized into alphabetical order and loose materials grouped by type of material by the archivist.
  - Committees, 1965 - 1969; F-11-3-1; 20 cm of textual records
    Architects Committee; Buildings and Site Committee; President's Committee on University Residences; Space Allocation and Planning Committee
    - Architects' Committee, 1968; F-11-3-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-72)
    - Architects' Committee, 1968; F-11-3-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-72)
    - Building and Site Committee Minutes, Part A, 1965 - 1967; F-11-3-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-72)
    - Building and Site Committee Minutes, Part B, 1965 - 1967; F-11-3-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-72)
    - Building and Site Committee Minutes, Part A, 1967 - 1968; F-11-3-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-72)
    - Building and Site Committee Minutes, Part B, 1967 - 1968; F-11-3-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-72)
    - Building and Site Committee Minutes, 1969; F-11-3-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-72)
    - Presidents' Committee on University Residences - minutes, 1967 - 1968; F-11-3-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-73)
    - Science Sub-Committee of Space Usage Committee - minutes, 1966 - 1968; F-11-3-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-73)
    - Space Usage Committee - Minutes, 1968; F-11-3-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 11-73)
  - Ancillary Services, 1968 - 1984; F-11-3-2; 5 cm of textual records
    Ancillary Services
    - Ancillary Services - Outgoing Correspondence, 1968 - 1979; F-11-3-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-73)
    - Ancillary Services - General, 1983 - 1984; F-11-3-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-73)
  - Subject files, 1964 - 1985; F-11-3-3; 1.4 m of textual records
    Animal Care Facility; BC Hydro; University Safety Committee
    - Air and Water Balance - Science Complex, 1966 - 1968; F-11-3-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-74)
    - Air and Water Balance - Theatre, 1965 - 1966; F-11-3-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-74)
    - Animal Care, 1981 - 1983; F-11-3-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-74)
    - Animal Care - Correspondence, Site Minutes, 1981 - 1982; F-11-3-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-74)
    - Animal Care - Change Orders, etc., 1982 - 1983; F-11-3-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-74)
    - AQ West Concourse, Outstanding Items, F-11-3-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-74)
    - AQ West Concourse, 1981 - 1982; F-11-3-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-74)
    - AQ West Concourse, Memos, Tenders, 1981; F-11-3-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-75)
    - AQ West Concourse, Correspondence, Site Minutes, 1982; F-11-3-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-75)
    - AQ West Concourse, General, 1981 - 1982; F-11-3-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 11-75)
    - AQ West Concourse, Change Orders, 1981; F-11-3-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 11-75)
    - BC Hydro Septic Tank, 1980 - 1981; F-11-3-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 11-75)
    - BC Hydro Septic Tank, 1981 - 1983; F-11-3-3-0-13 (Archival box - standard 11-75)
    - BC Hydro Septic Tank, 1982; F-11-3-3-0-14 (Archival box - standard 11-75)
    - BC Hydro Septic Tank Project, 1982; F-11-3-3-0-15 (Archival box - standard 11-75)
    - Boiler Plant Expansion, 1969; F-11-3-3-0-16 (Archival box - standard 11-75)
    - Budget Materials, 1968 - 1970; F-11-3-3-0-17 (Archival box - standard 11-75)
    - Central Mall - Mechanical Specs, 1966; F-11-3-3-0-18 (Archival box - standard 11-76)
    - Classroom Block, 1970; F-11-3-3-0-19 (Archival box - standard 11-76)
    - Classroom Block, Phase II, 1975; F-11-3-3-0-20 (Archival box - standard 11-76)
    - Classroom Block - Deficiencies, Phase I, 1970 - 1972; F-11-3-3-0-21 (Archival box - standard 11-76)
    - Classroom Block - Deficiencies, Phase I, 1972 - 1977; F-11-3-3-0-22 (Archival box - standard 11-76)
    - Classroom Block - Phase II Design Programme, 1972; F-11-3-3-0-23 (Archival box - standard 11-76)
    - Complaints, 1971 - 1984; F-11-3-3-0-24 (Archival box - standard 11-76)
    - Drawing Filing System, 1969 - 1972; F-11-3-3-0-25 (Archival box - standard 11-76)
    - Elevator Drawings, 1969 - 1972; F-11-3-3-0-26 (Archival box - standard 11-76)
    - Energy Data, 1979; F-11-3-3-0-27 (Archival box - standard 11-76)
    - Engineering Report - VHF/UHF Radio Equipment, 1981; F-11-3-3-0-28 (Archival box - standard 11-76)
    - Facilities Report, 1985; F-11-3-3-0-29 (Archival box - standard 11-76)
    - Fume Hoods, 1980; F-11-3-3-0-30 (Archival box - standard 11-76)
    - Fume Hoods, 1982 - 1983; F-11-3-3-0-31 (Archival box - standard 11-76)
    - Fume Hoods, Committee Report (D-33), 1983; F-11-3-3-0-32 (Archival box - standard 11-77)
    - Fume Hoods, Correspondence (48-01), 1980 - 1983; F-11-3-3-0-33 (Archival box - standard 11-77)
    - Fume Hoods, Data (D-362), 1972 - 1981; F-11-3-3-0-34 (Archival box - standard 11-77)
    - Fume Hoods, Discharge (#9), 1978 - 1983; F-11-3-3-0-35 (Archival box - standard 11-77)
    - Fume Hoods, Reports, 1981 - 1983; F-11-3-3-0-36 (Archival box - standard 11-77)
    - Fume Hoods, Safety, 1972 - 1981; F-11-3-3-0-37 (Archival box - standard 11-77)
    - Gym - Past Additions, 1971 - 1978; F-11-3-3-0-38 (Archival box - standard 11-77)
    - Heating System Development, 1973; F-11-3-3-0-39 (Archival box - standard 11-77)
    - Heating System Development, 1984; F-11-3-3-0-40 (Archival box - standard 11-77)
    - Heating System Investigation, 1973; F-11-3-3-0-41 (Archival box - standard 11-77)
    - Heating System Study, 1973; F-11-3-3-0-42 (Archival box - standard 11-77)
    - Housing, 1967; F-11-3-3-0-43 (Archival box - standard 11-77)
    - Housing, 1968 - 1969; F-11-3-3-0-44 (Archival box - standard 11-78)
    - Housing, 1971; F-11-3-3-0-45 (Archival box - standard 11-78)
    - Hydro Treatment Plant, 1981 - 1982; F-11-3-3-0-46 (Archival box - standard 11-78)
    - IMS Building, 1969 - 1979; F-11-3-3-0-47 (Archival box - standard 11-78)
    - Library Addition, Air and Water Balance, 1977; F-11-3-3-0-48 (Archival box - standard 11-78)
    - Mall Roof, 1971 - 1972; F-11-3-3-0-49 (Archival box - standard 11-78)
    - MPX II - Deficiencies, 1981 - 1985; F-11-3-3-0-50 (Archival box - standard 11-78)
    - MPX - Programme Phase, 1974; F-11-3-3-0-51 (Archival box - standard 11-78)
    - Multi-Purpose Complex, Phase II, 1981 - 1985; F-11-3-3-0-52 (Archival box - standard 11-78)
    - Parking Lot - Surface, 1980 - 1981; F-11-3-3-0-53 (Archival box - standard 11-78)
    - Parking Lot Lighting Part A, 1981 - 1982; F-11-3-3-0-54 (Archival box - standard 11-79)
    - Parking Lot Lighting Part B, 1981 - 1982; F-11-3-3-0-55 (Archival box - standard 11-79)
    - Pavilion Water Supply, 1980 - 1983; F-11-3-3-0-56 (Archival box - standard 11-79)
    - Physics Building - Testing and Balancing, 1980; F-11-3-3-0-57 (Archival box - standard 11-79)
    - Plant Study, 1969 - 1973; F-11-3-3-0-58 (Archival box - standard 11-79)
    - Presidents' House, 1983; F-11-3-3-0-59 (Archival box - standard 11-79)
    - Print Shop Proposal Part A, 1981 - 1983; F-11-3-3-0-60 (Archival box - standard 11-79)
    - Print Shop Proposal Part B, 1981 - 1983; F-11-3-3-0-61 (Archival box - standard 11-79)
    - Ring Road - Daily Progress Reports, Book 1, 1981 - 1982; F-11-3-3-0-62 (Archival box - standard 11-79)
    - Ring Road - Daily Progress Reports, Book 2, 1981 - 1982; F-11-3-3-0-63 (Archival box - standard 11-79)
    - Ring Road - Correspondence with Contractor and Site Dept. (33-07-06), 1981 - 1983; F-11-3-3-0-64 (Archival box - standard 11-80)
    - Ring Road - Weekly Report Field Memo, 1981 - 1982; F-11-3-3-0-65 (Archival box - standard 11-80)
    - Ring Road - Outstanding Items, 1981 - 1984; F-11-3-3-0-66 (Archival box - standard 11-80)
    - Ring Road - Outstanding, 1982 - 1983; F-11-3-3-0-67 (Archival box - standard 11-80)
    - Ring Road - General (33-07-01), 1967 - 1982; F-11-3-3-0-68
    - Ring Road - Progress Certificates, Weekly Reports Part A, 1981 - 1984; F-11-3-3-0-69 (Archival box - standard 11-80)
    - Ring Road - Progress Certificates, Weekly Reports Part B, 1981 - 1984; F-11-3-3-0-70 (Archival box - standard 11-80)
    - Ring Road - Goodbrand - Daily Extra Work Sheet, Memo, 1982; F-11-3-3-0-71 (Archival box - standard 11-81)
    - Ring Road - Correspondence with Engineer (33-07-02), 1981 - 1984; F-11-3-3-0-72 (Archival box - standard 11-81)
    - Ring Road - Interoffice Memo, 1981 - 1983; F-11-3-3-0-73 (Archival box - standard 11-81)
    - Ring Road - Site Meeting Minutes (33-07-10), 1981 - 1983; F-11-3-3-0-74 (Archival box - standard 11-81)
    - Ring Road - Services Part A (33-03), 1981 - 1983; F-11-3-3-0-75 (Archival box - standard 11-81)
    - Ring Road - Services Part B (33-03), 1981 - 1983; F-11-3-3-0-76 (Archival box - standard 11-81)
    - Safety, 1980 - 1982; F-11-3-3-0-77 (Archival box - standard 11-82)
    - Safety Committee - PP and P, 1978 - 1985; F-11-3-3-0-78 (Archival box - standard 11-82)
    - Safety Meetings, 1968 - 1979; F-11-3-3-0-79 (Archival box - standard 11-82)
    - Science Complex, Phase III Contract, 1968; F-11-3-3-0-80 (Archival box - standard 11-82)
    - Science Complex, Phase IV, 1976 - 1980; F-11-3-3-0-81 (Archival box - standard 11-82)
    - Science Complex - Deficiencies, Phase III, 1970 - 1977; F-11-3-3-0-82 (Archival box - standard 11-82)
    - Science Complex - Deficiencies, Phase IV, 1981 - 1982; F-11-3-3-0-83 (Archival box - standard 11-82)
    - Science Complex - Mod. of Heating, Phase II, 1969; F-11-3-3-0-84 (Archival box - standard 11-82)
    - Science Complex - Programme Phase, 1974 - 1976; F-11-3-3-0-85 (Archival box - standard 11-82)
    - Science Complex - Programme Phase, 1974 - 1976; F-11-3-3-0-86 (Archival box - standard 11-83)
    - Science Complex Renovations - Memos, Meeting Minutes, 1980 - 1982; F-11-3-3-0-87 (Archival box - standard 11-83)
    - Science Complex Renovations, 1981; F-11-3-3-0-88 (Archival box - standard 11-83)
    - Science Complex Renovations - Change Orders, 1981 - 1982; F-11-3-3-0-89 (Archival box - standard 11-83)
    - Shift Engineers Report, F-11-3-3-0-90 (Archival box - standard 11-83)
    - Shop Drawings - Boilers, 1964; F-11-3-3-0-91 (Archival box - standard 11-83)
    - Shop Drawings - Fans, 1965 - 1966; F-11-3-3-0-92 (Archival box - standard 11-83)
    - Space Studies, 1968 - 1970; F-11-3-3-0-93 (Archival box - standard 11-84)
    - TLX Problems, 1980 - 1982; F-11-3-3-0-94 (Archival box - standard 11-84)
    - Transportation Centre Skylight, 1971 - 1972; F-11-3-3-0-95 (Archival box - standard 11-84)
    - Transportation Problem, 1974 - 1980; F-11-3-3-0-96 (Archival box - standard 11-84)
    - Unit Sub-Station, 1965; F-11-3-3-0-97 (Archival box - standard 11-84)
    - Water Tower, 1980; F-11-3-3-0-98 (Archival box - standard 11-84)
    - Water Tower and Mains, 1968 - 1980; F-11-3-3-0-99 (Archival box - standard 11-84)
    - Water System - miscellaneous, 1974 - 1983; F-11-3-3-0-100 (Archival box - standard 11-84)
    - Water Tower Alarm, 1983; F-11-3-3-0-101 (Archival box - standard 11-84)
    - Water Tower Fire Flow/Watermains, 1974 - 1980; F-11-3-3-0-102 (Archival box - standard 11-84)
    - Water Tower Fire Main, 1972 - 1980; F-11-3-3-0-103 (Archival box - standard 11-84)
    - Work Orders System and Other Reviews, 1974 - 1975; F-11-3-3-0-104 (Archival box - standard 11-84)
    - Work Order Cost Comparisons, 1983 - 1984; F-11-3-3-0-105 (Archival box - standard 11-84)
  - Bound contracts, reports and specification books, 1960 - 1984; F-11-3-4; 1 m of textual records
    - Contract documents - Ring Road and Parking Lot, 1981; F-11-3-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-85)
    - Contract documents - Parking Lots B and C Lighting, 1981; F-11-3-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-85)
    - Contract documents - Playing Field 3, 1983; F-11-3-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-85)
    - Contract documents - Playing Field 3, 1983; F-11-3-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-85)
    - Contract documents - Playing Field 3, 1983; F-11-3-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-85)
    - Physical Plant - Maintenance and Operations: Goals, Organization and Planning, 1973; F-11-3-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-85)
    - Physical Plant - Maintenance and Operations Division Annual Report, 1972 - 1973; F-11-3-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-85)
    - Physical Plant - Organization, Responsibilities and Objectives, 1973; F-11-3-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-85)
    - Physical Plant - Annual Reports, 1972 - 1970; F-11-3-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-85)
    - Physical Plant - Annual Report, Central Stores Review, 1974 - 1975; F-11-3-4-0-10 (Archival box - standard 11-85)
    - Proposals - Arena, 1969; F-11-3-4-0-11 (Archival box - standard 11-86)
    - Proposals - Discovery Parks Inc, 1979; F-11-3-4-0-12 (Archival box - standard 11-86)
    - Proposals - Discovery Park Development Area Primary Servicing, 1979; F-11-3-4-0-13 (Archival box - standard 11-86)
    - Proposals - Ice Skating Facility Study, 1973; F-11-3-4-0-14 (Archival box - standard 11-86)
    - Proposals - Library Additions, 1971; F-11-3-4-0-15 (Archival box - standard 11-86)
    - Proposals - Library Additions, 1973; F-11-3-4-0-16 (Archival box - standard 11-86)
    - Proposals - Multi-Purpose Facility, Feasibility Study, 1971; F-11-3-4-0-17 (Archival box - standard 11-86)
    - Proposals - Multi-Purpose Facility, Feasibility Study, 1971; F-11-3-4-0-18 (Archival box - standard 11-86)
    - Proposals - Multi-Purpose Facility, Site Evaluation, 1971; F-11-3-4-0-19 (Archival box - standard 11-86)
    - Proposals - Simon Fraser Townsite Plan, Preliminary, 1966; F-11-3-4-0-20 (Archival box - standard 11-86)
    - Proposals - Simon Fraser Townsite Plan, 1966; F-11-3-4-0-21 (Archival box - standard 11-86)
    - Proposals - Village, F-11-3-4-0-22 (Archival box - standard 11-86)
    - Proposals - West Mall Complex, Program and Conceptual Design, 1982; F-11-3-4-0-23 (Archival box - standard 11-86)
    - Proposals - Winter Sports Facility, 1973; F-11-3-4-0-24 (Archival box - standard 11-86)
    - Architectural reports and programs - Animal Care Facility, 1974; F-11-3-4-0-25 (Archival box - standard 11-87)
    - Architectural reports and programs - Architectural Competition, 1963; F-11-3-4-0-26 (Archival box - standard 11-87)
    - Architectural reports and programs - Day Care Centre, 1973; F-11-3-4-0-27 (Archival box - standard 11-87)
    - Architectural reports and programs - Day Care Centre, 1974; F-11-3-4-0-28 (Archival box - standard 11-87)
    - Architectural reports and programs - Gymnasium Expansion, 1972; F-11-3-4-0-29 (Archival box - standard 11-87)
    - Architectural reports and programs - Housing - S.F.U. Housing Plans, 1967 - 1971; F-11-3-4-0-30 (Archival box - standard 11-87)
    - Architectural reports and programs - S.F.U. Competition, F-11-3-4-0-31 (Archival box - standard 11-87)
      Reviewed for access (Jan 9, 2024) – File is open, no restricted information identified.
    - Architectural reports and programs - S.F.U. Development Plan, 1963; F-11-3-4-0-32 (Archival box - standard 11-87)
    - Architectural reports and programs - S.F.U. Development Plan, 1963; F-11-3-4-0-33 (Archival box - standard 11-87)
    - Architectural reports and programs - S.F.U. Development Plan, Phase II, 1965; F-11-3-4-0-34 (Archival box - standard 11-87)
    - Architectural reports and programs - S.F.U. Planning, 1973; F-11-3-4-0-35 (Archival box - standard 11-87)
    - Architectural reports and programs - S.F.U. Progress Report, 1966; F-11-3-4-0-36 (Archival box - standard 11-87)
    - Architectural reports and programs - Ski Chalet - Preliminary Proposal for Renovations, 1973; F-11-3-4-0-37 (Archival box - standard 11-87)
    - Architectural reports and programs - Tennis Court Construction, 1970; F-11-3-4-0-38 (Archival box - standard 11-87)
    - Miscellaneous reports - Acoustical Studies, 1970 - 1972; F-11-3-4-0-39 (Archival box - standard 11-88)
    - Miscellaneous reports - Campus Dynamic Control, 1981; F-11-3-4-0-40 (Archival box - standard 11-88)
    - Miscellaneous reports - Food Service Study, 1968; F-11-3-4-0-41 (Archival box - standard 11-88)
    - Miscellaneous reports - Funicular Railway, 1971; F-11-3-4-0-42 (Archival box - standard 11-88)
    - Miscellaneous reports - Health Needs, F-11-3-4-0-43 (Archival box - standard 11-88)
    - Miscellaneous reports - Technical Shops and Stores, 1969; F-11-3-4-0-44 (Archival box - standard 11-88)
    - Miscellaneous reports - U.C.B. Committee Interim Report, 1972; F-11-3-4-0-45 (Archival box - standard 11-88)
    - Miscellaneous reports - U.C.B. - Brief to be Presented to Board of Governors, 1970; F-11-3-4-0-46 (Archival box - standard 11-88)
    - Site investigations - Proposed Classroom Block, 1966; F-11-3-4-0-47 (Archival box - standard 11-88)
    - Site investigations - Proposed Men's Residence, 1966; F-11-3-4-0-48 (Archival box - standard 11-88)
    - Site investigations - Proposed Women's Residence, 1965; F-11-3-4-0-49 (Archival box - standard 11-88)
    - Specifications - Gymnasium - Swimming Pool, 1964; F-11-3-4-0-50 (Archival box - standard 11-89)
      Access review (Jun 17, 2022) – File is open, no restricted information identified.
    - Specifications - Millwork, Women's Residence, 1965; F-11-3-4-0-51 (Archival box - standard 11-89)
    - Specifications - Theatre, 1965; F-11-3-4-0-52 (Archival box - standard 11-89)
    - Specifications - Gymnasium - Swimming Pool, 1965; F-11-3-4-0-53 (Archival box - standard 11-89)
    - Specifications - Central Mall, 1965; F-11-3-4-0-54 (Archival box - standard 11-89)
    - Specifications - Roads and Parking Lots, 1965; F-11-3-4-0-55 (Archival box - standard 11-89)
    - Specifications - Library Building, 1965; F-11-3-4-0-56 (Archival box - standard 11-89)
    - Specifications - Additions to Pool, 1965; F-11-3-4-0-57 (Archival box - standard 11-89)
    - Specifications - Science Complex Phase II, 1965; F-11-3-4-0-58 (Archival box - standard 11-89)
    - Specifications - Science Complex Phase II, 1965; F-11-3-4-0-59 (Archival box - standard 11-89)
    - Specifications - Library, Phase II, 1966; F-11-3-4-0-60 (Archival box - standard 11-89)
    - Specifications - Men's Residence, 1966; F-11-3-4-0-61 (Archival box - standard 11-89)
    - Specifications - Boiler House and Mains, 1966; F-11-3-4-0-62 (Archival box - standard 11-90)
    - Specifications - Parking Lot, 1966; F-11-3-4-0-63 (Archival box - standard 11-90)
    - Specifications - Staff Parking Lot, 1966; F-11-3-4-0-64 (Archival box - standard 11-90)
    - Specifications - Boiler House Addition, 1966; F-11-3-4-0-65 (Archival box - standard 11-90)
    - Specifications - Learning Resources Area, Library, 1966; F-11-3-4-0-66 (Archival box - standard 11-90)
    - Specifications - Rough Grading and Services to Northside CC, 1960; F-11-3-4-0-67 (Archival box - standard 11-90)
    - Specifications - Northside Classroom Complex, 1966 - 1967; F-11-3-4-0-68 (Archival box - standard 11-90)
    - Specifications - Science Complex, Phase III, 1967; F-11-3-4-0-69 (Archival box - standard 11-90)
    - Specifications - Science Complex Phase III, 1968; F-11-3-4-0-70 (Archival box - standard 11-90)
    - Specifications - Extension of West Campus Mains, 1968; F-11-3-4-0-71 (Archival box - standard 11-90)
    - Specifications - West Campus Mains, 1968; F-11-3-4-0-72 (Archival box - standard 11-90)
    - Specifications - Student Housing Site Services, 1968; F-11-3-4-0-73 (Archival box - standard 11-91)
    - Specifications - Science Complex, Phase III, 1968; F-11-3-4-0-74 (Archival box - standard 11-91)
    - Specifications - Parking Lot B, 1969; F-11-3-4-0-75 (Archival box - standard 11-91)
    - Specifications - Additions to Boiler Plant, 1969; F-11-3-4-0-76 (Archival box - standard 11-91)
    - Specifications - Academic Services Building, 1970; F-11-3-4-0-77 (Archival box - standard 11-91)
    - Specifications - Extension of Parking Lot B, 1970; F-11-3-4-0-78 (Archival box - standard 11-91)
    - Specifications - Extension of Parking Lot B, 1970; F-11-3-4-0-79 (Archival box - standard 11-91)
    - Specifications - Science Complex Workshops, 1970; F-11-3-4-0-80 (Archival box - standard 11-91)
    - Specifications - Parking Lot A, 1971; F-11-3-4-0-81 (Archival box - standard 11-91)
    - Specifications - Discovery Park Road, 1980; F-11-3-4-0-82 (Archival box - standard 11-91)
    - Specifications - AQ Alterations, 1981; F-11-3-4-0-83 (Archival box - standard 11-92)
    - Specifications - Science Complex, 1981; F-11-3-4-0-84 (Archival box - standard 11-92)
    - Specifications - Science Complex, 1981; F-11-3-4-0-85 (Archival box - standard 11-92)
    - Specifications - Playfield No. 5, F-11-3-4-0-86 (Archival box - standard 11-92)
    - Specifications - Centre for the Arts Renovation, 1984; F-11-3-4-0-87 (Archival box - standard 11-92)
    - Landscape specifications - Residences, 1969; F-11-3-4-0-88 (Archival box - standard 11-92)
    - Landscape specifications - Ring Road Reclamation, Phase II, 1983; F-11-3-4-0-89 (Archival box - standard 11-92)
    - Landscape specifications - Science Complex Courtyards, F-11-3-4-0-90 (Archival box - standard 11-92)
  - Telephone Directories, 1965 - 2005; F-11-3-5; 38 cm of textual records
    - Telephone directories, 1965 - 1985; F-11-3-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-113)
    - Telephone directories, 1986 - 1996; F-11-3-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-114)
    - Telephone directories, 1997 - 2005; F-11-3-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-115)
- Concordia Management, 1974 - 1980; F-11-4; 2.51 m of textual records
  Series consists of the construction records of Concordia Management, the project managers for the construction of the University's Multipurpose Complex. It includes correspondence and construction documents such as contracts, change and variation orders, progress reports, site minutes, and deficiency lists.
  - The JH McRae Co. Ltd. (CB-00.2), 1977; F-11-4-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-93)
  - United Contractors Ltd. (CB-01.2), 1975 - 1976; F-11-4-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-93)
  - Credit and Extras United Contractors Ltd. (CB-01.4), 1974 - 1976; F-11-4-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-93)
  - Elevators (CB-02.1), 1977; F-11-4-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-93)
  - Montgomery Elevator Co. Ltd. (CB-02.2), 1977 - 1979; F-11-4-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-93)
  - Materials testing Bailey Labs Ltd. (CB-03), 1977 - 1978; F-11-4-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-93)
  - Material Testing (CB-03.1), 1977; F-11-4-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-93)
  - Structural and Architectural Concrete (CB-04.1b), 1977; F-11-4-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-93)
  - Prosseger Construction, Part A (CB-04.2), 1977 - 1980; F-11-4-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-94)
  - Prosseger Construction, SFU Architectural and Structural Concrete (CB-04.3), 1977 - 1978; F-11-4-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 11-94)
  - Prosseger Construction, Work Orders (CB-04.3), 1977 - 1978; F-11-4-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 11-94)
  - Prosseger Construction, Part B (CB-04.2), 1977 - 1980; F-11-4-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 11-94)
  - Prosseger Construction, (CB-04.2), 1977 - 1978; F-11-4-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 11-94)
  - Mechanical Specs (CB-05), 1976; F-11-4-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 11-94)
  - Mechanical Work: MPX Mechanical Installations (CB-05), 1978; F-11-4-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 11-94)